I'm hoping my voice is going to be okay, but it's been so husky today I'm gonna
lose my
voice a bit, so hopefully we'll be all right.
But yeah, thank you for coming ladies and today's call was all about ethical
seduction
and sexuality. Something that we haven't really done up to now which is crazy
really because
we talk so much about the sort of non-sexual elements of calm, but it's good to
talk about
this stuff as well, isn't it? So I'm glad we're doing this cool thing.
So why seduction? Why are we talking about seduction today? So like I said, we
do so
so much training on styles of coming and all of the non-sexual ways to keep
your clients
engaged, but we can also acknowledge that we are in the business of seduction
and it's
okay to be sexual on cam. It's never expected from us as a group, but if you
want to engage
in central and sexual acts on webcam, it's great to share advice and learn from
each
other about the best ways to do so.
So hopefully we might all sort of chip in and talk about some of the things
that we might
be interested in doing or that we've thought about or that we've done or that
we're curious
about so that we can help each other, you know, learn from each other.
Do you want to do this slide?
Yeah. Before I start, can I just say, is it the too loud where I am or because
I'm just
outside in a terrain, but if it's too loud, I'll go inside.
No, I'm tired, I'm tired. Okay. Just wanted to check. Thank you. Okay then. So
why do we
focus on ethics?
Women's power of seduction has been long demonized and seen as a weapon against
men. From the
days of burning witches at the stake to the modern day shame and stigma around
sex work,
the patriarchal fear of women with power and finding ways to shame women out of
use in
their divine sexual power to their advantage here, the ethical community, we
hope to help
many women change their relationship to their sexual power, contrary to public
beliefs.
This doesn't mean we have to take advantage of men or use our sexuality to
control them.
It means that once, sorry, it means that that once we can find a channel to
power, sorry,
I'm just getting a little bit in, a little bit everywhere, sorry girls. Okay.
Okay. It
means that once we find and channel our power, we can offer it through as a
gift to our clients
and it can benefit us and nourish them. So it's not a power struggle and
everybody wins.
Now, this is one thing that I feel like I really like, I hate that we have to
put on
us like, you know, we're just trying to take advantage of the men or whatever
else. Obviously
it's not like that. We're not forcing anyone to do it. They're coming to us for
our services
and we're providing them a safe space to explore their fantasies and whatnot.
So never feel
bad about using your sexual energy to, you know, give these clients the best
time because
that's basically what they're doing and there's there we all win, you know, we
win because
obviously we're getting more regular clients and getting paid to do it and also
enjoying
it hopefully. And of course, the client wins because they're getting to just
explore, you
know, this side of themselves that maybe they wouldn't with anybody else. So
yes, I'll
pass you on to the next slide now. Yeah, yeah. And I think, I think even like,
same, it's
not a power struggle. I mean, when you're on camera, you might be playing with
power,
you know, you might be playing with domination or being submissive. But it
doesn't mean even
if you're doing those things, it doesn't mean that there's a power imbalance
with who is,
you know, with your worthiness, we're all just as worthy and we're all
benefiting benefiting
from it. So yeah, I think there's a lot of stuff in society about like somebody
's got
to be controlled, somebody's got to be wrong, somebody's got to be winning.
Naturally, it's
not like that at all. Like, you know, it can be just a collaboration with your
clients
about what you're doing. And if it's consensual. Okay, so being seductive on
camp, what does
it look like? So some of the ways that you can be seductive and use your
sexuality on
camp. So body language and movement. And so of course we can use our body
language. And
how we show up, you know, we've got this little box to work with, we can we can
use that to
our advantage. So we can sort of think about the ways that we want to show up
on what sort
of role we're portraying. And we can, you know, use our bodies and use our
movement in different
ways. You know, sometimes I like to, you know, we'll do a twill or, you know,
there's different
ways that we can use our body in the space to entice them into our world and to
, and to
seduce them. And using our words and actions. So of course, the way that we
speak is part
of our power of seduction, the words that we use, the tone of our voice, and or
, you know,
the things that we're typing, if we're not speaking of the microphone. And the
things
that we do, so we'll talk a little bit more about the actual acts, like sexual
act and
sensual acts. Of course, they're part of seduction as well. And using your own
sensuality and
your own pleasure. And so I think it's part of a bit of a trap that a lot of
people knew
girls to come get stuck in, is that they think that they're just there for the
man's pleasure,
and they're just trying to figure out what the man wants all the time. But
actually,
if you can start from your own place of pleasure, and what feels good to you,
that's just going
to translate to come and get you get firstly, get you the customers that you
actually want
because you're doing things you actually enjoy doing. And secondly, just makes
for much longer
calls, better connections, regulars, because they're actually checking into
your energy
that's something you enjoy. And that's something that's more than words and
actions, isn't
it? That's about energy. If you're actually enjoying it, you'll bring them that
energy
and that is seductive. The pacing and command of the room, sometimes being sed
uctive looks
like being able to slow down a conversation, or being able to get more fast-
paced and energetic.
You know, so the way that you show up in the room will be your command of the
room and
will have a lot to do with how you're seducing. Power dynamics. So yeah, power
dynamics are
a big part of being seductive. As we said before, we know the different styles
of coming
that sometimes we can be dominant, sometimes we can be submissive, but we can
always be
seductive in whatever type of power dynamic is in the room. We can still hold
our own power.
Even when we're being submissive, we can still be seductive by holding our own
power and
knowing our own worth and really letting ourselves, giving ourselves permission
to be
in that role, you know. And the introduction on camera might look like slowly
building
up the tension. So whether that's in the things that you're doing, you know,
the things that
you're showing, how much of yourself you're showing, or the things that you're
talking
about, like, I know I talk a lot about building up fantasies, but you know,
that's something
I really like to do to be seductive, is to use the power of suggestion. So
slowly more
and more of a fantasy, or slowly getting more and more out of their fantasy, so
that this,
you know, hanging on your every word and talking to you for much longer, so
part of the art
discussion is building up the tension. And then the benefits, so there are of
course
are so many benefits to just acknowledging your, how you're being seductive,
and being
seductive on camera has so many benefits for you and the clients. So the
clients can feel
safe, connected, and enticed. It's an invitation into fantasy, or into whatever
role you're
playing. You can go at your own pace. The session might be longer if you're,
you know,
you've got more of, if you're honing down on being seductive, the sessions
could be
longer, because you're not rushing. And, and your sex appeal is centered, which
can build
your confidence. So if you're able to slow down and think about your own
pleasure, think
about your words and actions, slowly build up tension, you know, those are all
things
which will give you more of a command of your, of your space and help you to
feel more
confident, ultimately. Okay. Um, Jade, you want, do you want to just read this
one? And
then maybe we'll talk about this together, like the different, the different
styles.
Yeah. So how to be seductive in each kind of style? So doctrine is tempting
someone into
a new, into a narrative slash role. Using your power of seduction, you can
invite someone
to feel a certain way. How won't we be seductive in a different kind of styles?
So the ones
that we're going to discuss today are domination, girl next door, pony house
wife, curious student,
and fantasy facilitator. So I would say, I'll start with domination, of course,
because
this is what I do. I would say to be seductive in domination. The first thing
that just popped
into my head, I don't know why it was just the clothes that you're wearing and
like the
outfits. And like, I just thought about rubbing my body when I got latex on
because they love
to hear the sounds of the latex, like this freaky sound that it makes. Um, so
that's
something that I might do. So, or, you know, for example, if I'm wearing like,
I had boots
that also are like PVC or latex, you know, showing them the boots and stuff
like that.
So just showing them the different part of the outfit that I'm wearing. And
that's probably
one of the first things I would do as a dominatrix to be seductive on cam,
because doing domination,
you may be not doing as many of the sexual acts as you would be if you're doing
the overalls.
So there's like different ways of being seductive rather than just doing the
sexual act. So
like I said, focusing on the clothes and then maybe, you know, you remove them
little by
little, but, um, but yeah, that's what I would do for domination for sure. Yeah
. Yeah, I was
thinking about girl next door and I was thinking, I think for me, because I did
do, I did start
off with being like girl next door for a while, which was kind of in line with
what I was because
I was that like I was just learning about things and I was. And I think part of
the seduction
in that part of inviting someone to feel a certain way with the girl next door
is inviting them
into your curiosity. You know, a way of being seductive is to be curious, you
know, is to be
a bit shy, but also a bit a bit open and a little bit curious about whatever it
is that they're
bringing to you, what you might like to explore. Um, and yeah, curiosity can be
really seductive,
I think when we're thinking about girl next door, um, because you're inviting
them to feel like
they're holding a space for you, they're inviting you into this world. Um, and,
and that can come
across in the way that you, you might sort of ask your clients what kind of
things, you know, other
girls wear on cam and what kind of things people do and how, how I wonder, you
know, what, what
could I wear maybe next time I'm here or what are some of the things that you
talk about,
you know, on cam with people or, you know, just being really curious and
stepping into that role
is a way to be seductive because it's playing a role, isn't it? Um, um, I think
, well, fantasy
facilitator, I put that on there because I mean, it's something that's better
mouthful, isn't it?
But because I think that's largely what I do on cam. So that's where I feel
like I fit, even though
I fit into a few of these boxes. Um, but I think to be seductive in that is to
be open. Like, I feel
like what makes me seductive is that I can build on other people's ideas. So I
'm not quickly jumping
to think I know what they want. I'm not quickly jumping to sort of show up in a
way I think they
might want. I'm just slowing the pace, really listening, um, just being open to
whatever it is
they're bringing and then thinking to myself, okay, how can I, how can I
facilitate their fantasy
in the best way? Like, what is it about me that makes them want to talk to me
about this thing?
You know, are they talking to me about someone who, you know, they, they felt
like a control
with and how can I gradually build that into the way I'm talking to them. Um,
so yeah, I think part
of being seductive in the, you know, with other being a fantasy facilitator is
being open. And part
of that comes with confidence because, you know, when you're not feeling
confident, it's easy to
just pressure yourself to have to see something quick or to have to respond
quickly. But with
confidence, you can start to slow down and listen more attentively. And that is
seductive, I think,
for a lot of people, because it shows them that they can show up here how they
want to and it's
going to be okay with you, you know. Um, does anyone, does anyone else have any
ideas or anything
to say about the different styles or what they might do and how they think sed
uction
what comes into it? I think that maybe something that can be used for all
styles is like eye contact.
So of course, like you're not looking directly into the eyes, but you can like
just look down your
camera and like really just, you know, you have like a little sexy love and
little cheeky smile and
maybe like, you know, playing with your hair or something like that. But like,
I think eye contact
could be like a really good one for seduction. And obviously you can use that
in all roles,
like in all different camp styles, whatever one you're doing. Um, but yeah.
Yeah, I think that's such a good point. Yeah. And also thinking about your
environment.
So I know you've got like those lovely backlights, haven't you, that are
the ad to that, that, you know, how seductive your camera room is because the
lighting is really
seductive. Yeah. Yeah. And even just like having things in the background, like
some people have
toys in the background or things in the background that are like an invitation,
aren't they to
think about, you know, in invitations, think about what might happen or, you
know, think about
the possibilities and yeah, that can be seductive as well. I think as well,
maybe I are breathing
on cam, like, so say you've got your mic on, but even if you're not talking,
sometimes they still
want to have your mic on so they can hear what's going on around you. And
obviously hear your
breathing if you giggle and stuff like that. So maybe you can, if the
conversations, you know,
getting a bit more heated, you can start to like make your breath a little bit
more like, like,
you know, that you're getting really excited. And like, this is where your
actor will come out
or not. Maybe you actually are getting excited, which is great if you are fully
enjoying it like
that. And then also like a cheeky little giggle as well. I mean, I'm sure that
they would like
that depends on, you know, where the conversation's going. And again, they can
probably be used for
all different cam styles. Yeah. Yeah, that's such a good point. And that is
something that I do
all the time because I'm very, very talk on cam, but I always have my audio on.
And I always like,
do do deep breaths if we're talking about something that's like, you know, more
funny,
I'll be like, I'll change my breathing. And they can tell and a lot of the time
they'll comment on
it as well. Um, yeah. Yeah. I mean, sometimes it's genuine. Not not all of that
. Um,
okay. Yeah. Okay. Let's move on to the next one. So I wonder if we could share
some ideas
about, you know, not just seduction, but about how we bring our sexuality into
cam, you know,
sexual acts and things that we might do or that we're curious about on. Um,
because it's not
something we often talk about, is it? And I think it's okay to talk about it.
You know,
we should feel that we can remove some of that shame and talk about some of the
things that we
do and get inspiration from each other. Um, and it doesn't have to be like, you
know,
like, for instance, one thing that I like to do is, uh, to put oil on my body,
like I feel like that's quite sexual acts and quite seductive. And sometimes I
'll do it with like
lingerie on or whatever. And sometimes I'll take it off. But yeah, that's just
one thing that I,
that I often use and it's easy. I kind of, if I'm feeling a bit lazy, I might
just have some oil
next to me. Cause I know that that's like, if I, if I don't have as much
capacity for conversation
or whatever, I just know that that's an easy thing and it looks really good on
cam. Um, so yeah,
that's an easy thing to make some idea. But we all think it's just the best.
Like, I also do that
when I also think, or what do I even say to this one? I'm like, Oh, I just kept
the oil out. I'm just
learning and I love that. And I just love it. Um, but something I would
actually do on cam to
if I'm going to be seductive is I would probably dance. Like I do some like,
maybe like some sexy
dancing for them. I love it myself. Cause I don't actually think I can dance at
all. But you know,
you just, you just want it as you do. So I probably just take me, like, you
know,
shape it to my body slowly as I'm dancing and like, you know, maybe put the
strap down and put it back
up. And I don't know, just really like, I really play it all for ages. Like,
when I'm doing anything
on camera, build it up for a long time before anything ever happens. So if the
dance would be
a part of that, because that'll help to like, you know, build up the tension
kind of thing.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And of course, there's like, there's like the events, toys
and stuff. Isn't
there that they've been a lot of people have been chatting in the group about
this week.
Um, so of course you can use like all different types of toys. Like there's so
many different
toys you can use. But yeah, like certain toys you can connect with your cam as
well. So that they
can, they can feel like they've got some, you know, involvement with what you
're doing and what
you're experiencing. So with that toy, actually, when you connect it to the cam
, I've never used
this one on cam before. So I'm not sure how it works fully. Did they actually,
are they able to
control that and make your fibres that are sitting level or this or that? Or
when they tape it
actually like does something to you? Is that what it is? I think that's what
the girls are
saying when the tips maybe and they tip it like vibrate or, I don't know, the
toy moves or
something like that. So yeah, if you do use toys on cam, then that would be a
good one to
to invest in. I think a few of the girls actually bought one last week just
because you noticed
that the overgills had done so well with the toy. So a few of the girls have
bought one. So, um,
yeah, I think that one does work well because like Elle said, the clients
actually get involved
with that one. So they must love it because, you know, it feels like they'd
actually get into like
do something to you, you know, they're not, you know what I mean? Yeah, yeah,
because a couple
of the girls said they would just leave it next to them on the sofa or whatever
and, you know,
be buzzing so you don't actually have to have it in. They just think that they
're, they just think
that they're controlling it. Is anyone used one? If anyone here used one of
those on cam?
No. No. Yeah. Yeah, so that's, that's one of the things that feels popular at
the moment.
Yeah. Any other ideas of things to use or things to do on cam? One, one thing
that I've done before,
which is obviously dependent on what you're talking about. There is used rope.
So I quite like
Shabari, like rope play and stuff and, you know, a lot of clients would like
that as well. But
you can do like the most basic ties on yourself. And you can have a look like
on YouTube and it
shows you how to do a really basic, it's got the name of it that's like a boob,
not basically
like a breast tie and it just ties in between here and goes around and it looks
really good.
That's one thing that you can do on cam and it's also, it is seductive because
it's slow
and you can, there's a sound. So you can, they can hear the sound a bit playing
and, you know,
you're doing it and then you can talk to them about how it's like restrictive
and don't have
to be naked to do it. You can be obviously, but it also looks good if you're
wearing like
silk pyjamas or something that's a different, like a contrasting material to
the rope that
you're using. Yeah. So that's something that I've done on cam a few times and
quite like to do.
Love that. I just had a vision in my head of you being all naked tied up and
you couldn't
untie yourself. Oh god, that was happened to me. If I was trying to do rope on
cam, I'd probably
just end up tying myself up and not be able to get off. But I love that though.
I love Shabari
and I'm, yeah, like I said, the clients would love that too. Yeah. Yeah. And
there's a, there's other,
there's other sort of things that you can do. Of course, if you're like being
submissive, you can
obviously use things on yourself, can't you? You can use like, well, anything
really, but you can use
like whips or like little something that's for a bit of impact play, you know,
like a paddle or
whatever. It doesn't, you don't need to be doing it hard because they can't
tell. But yeah,
you can give them some control over, you know, what you're experiencing, which
can be really
sort of safe and can, I've had some clients that really love that and will do
it for a very long
time, really slowly. So that's good for, you know, those long calls. Yeah,
because there's a way
of doing it isn't there with like the, like the whipping and stuff where you do
it over a long
time and you have you hated that difference, you get the right client, they can
tell you how to do
properly. So if you like spank yourself at like different intensities and it
starts to go a bit
norms, and then you can, you can like go for longer and stuff like that, like
there's like a full
thing. So yeah, so that can be really dragged out for a long time. And like El
ge says, like, you
don't actually have to hit yourself harder, you don't want to, or maybe you do,
maybe you're like
it, you know? Yeah, yeah, I just thought that, sorry, go ahead. No, go on. I'm
just going to say
maybe another way of being disruptive is to leave them wanting more as well. So
as it gets towards
the end of the session, maybe start to chat about something else, or I don't
know, it's maybe something
else will come up and then you could say, Oh yeah, like let's explore that next
time, you know, or
maybe we'll explore that next time. So then they're like, Oh wow, like we've
got something else to do
next time. Of course, you want to give them, you know, enough in the session to
be happy with,
but then you want them to come back. So yeah, just leave them something like an
element of mystery
for what could happen next time. Think that the face is up to for sure. And
obviously can be used
with all calm styles. Yeah, yeah, definitely. And another thing I think that is
you can use
and be playful with is like, when there's more than one client in your camera,
you know, if you know,
if you know one or more of the clients quite well, you can be like, you can
play on that.
I think that was so, I don't know, I don't know, it's meant to attend it on or
not.
Oh, I think maybe, sorry. Sorry. Okay, it's okay. Yeah, so thinking about,
thinking about teasing and like, seduction, as in, I might have a client who
comes into my room
talks me about something and I can see that another client is watching. And
then when they
leave, I'll say to that one, you know, oh, this is what I was doing, or this is
how it made me feel,
or, you know, I wouldn't do that with them, but maybe we can talk about this
kind of thing.
So you can use like one client to sort of set you up for something with another
one, you know what
I mean? Yeah, yeah. And I suppose it's not even just about what you actually do
on cam. It's about
your content as well, and what you share on your profile, and what you talk
about, and the photos
that you've got, you know, that's part of seducing, isn't it, like inviting
people into an idea about
yourself. But yeah, focus on that as well. Yeah, because suppose we have to sed
uce them first with
the profile before we actually get the chance to, because they're going to see
the profile before
they see us always, like, so yes, we want to make sure our profile is very
inviting and stuff, and
but yeah, we can help with this as well with new girls or whatever else or any
girls, of course,
anyone who needs any help with that. But I think Nail and the profile is like,
going to barely set it aside from how well you do on cam, because of course,
once they're in your
room and you see how amazing you are, they're going to want to keep coming back
, but to actually get
them in your room in the first place, it's the profile's job of that, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so is anybody else got any things that they want to share or questions
that they want to ask
about being sensual or sexual on cam? You can put it in the chat box if you don
't quite want to speak
up. No? I just had a thought actually as well, one more thing about seduction,
like what to do.
You could put on some seductive music in the background. So again, if you've
got your mic on,
of course, I mean, even if you haven't, do that for yourself anywhere if you
want to. But then,
obviously, if you've got your mic on, you can have on some, like, really slow,
sensual music,
or, you know, and then obviously the client can hear that too, so it kind of
creates like,
you're doing the same environment kind of thing, because you're both hearing
the same thing,
you know what I mean? So that could be sort of what you do as well. Yeah. Yeah,
there's a lot in
there about using the senses, I guess, isn't there? Like thinking about what
they're seeing
and hearing and feeling using the senses to happen to how to seduce them.
Yeah. Okay, ladies. Well, it doesn't look like we have any questions. Is there
anything else
anyone wants to add or ask as while we're here? Of course, you know, this sort
of thing, you can
always speak to your mentor about, and you can always message one of us, and I
'm sure we'd always
be happy to answer any questions that you've got. But yeah, is there anything
else anyone
like to add? No? Okay. No? Okay. Well, it's been lovely to see you all. It's
been lovely to see
you all, and we've got, well, we'll post, we'll post about when the next call
is that we've got
coming up in the group. So, yeah, hopefully we'll see you all very soon. Have
the next call.
Thank you for coming along, ladies. And let's all guess the doctor, shall we,
and see how we get on
and share with each other? Yeah. Yeah, absolutely. I was just saying it's
helped her. Thank you,
thank you for leaving. Good to see you. And yeah, we'll see you all very soon.
Thank you, ladies.
Hi, everyone. Have a good evening. Thank you. Love you. Bye. Bye.